

CV ANDRA VOINEA

I bring 8 years of combined expertise in **graphic design** and front-end development (~4 years full-time in design, mostly web, and prior to that, 4 years full-time in front-end development).

shapespin@gmail.com +40 772 167 296 <u>behance.net/lightscapesUI</u>

HARD SKILLS

- Figma, Adobe XD/Illustrator/Photoshop/Indesign
- · HTML, CSS, WordPress, basic JavaScript and PHP

EXPERIENCE

VISUAL DESIGNER @ IN2IT CREATIVE LAB BUCHAREST

12/2019-07/2023

- Innovative Web Design: Spearheaded the design of over 15 responsive websites and web
 applications of different types (business, personal, portfolio, non-profit, employment,
 portal) tailored to the unique needs of each client. These include: Apsis, Apsisware,
 ArniaDb, BereaTNR, In2it, JobShark, Odeen, Mălina Mîndruţescu, Modig, Techtalent,
 TestUrbis and WikiArnia.
- Branding Excellence: Redefined the visual identity for 10+ clients by creating memorable logos, stationery, and comprehensive brand books. Clients include: Apsis, ArniaDB, BereaTNR, Brezzels, MedicPlan, Modig, Odeen, Test Urbis and Zeren.
- Strategic Research and Content Creation: Wrote the agency's blog researching design topics (in2it.ro/blog)
- Peer Collaboration and Leadership: Conducted monthly design review sessions, fostering
 a collaborative environment that encouraged creativity and continuous improvement
 among the design team. This initiative enhanced the overall quality of design output.

GRAPHIC DESIGN TEACHER @ TITU MAIORESCU UNIVERSITY BUCHAREST

03-06/2019

 Taught graphic design classes and workshops to second-year students enrolled in the "Communication and Public Relations" bachelor's program.

FREELANCE VISUAL DESIGNER

01/2014-Present

- Created diverse graphic design materials (posters, infographics, logos, annual reports, newsletters, greeting cards) for NGO's such as Iniţiativa România, 80east, Fundaţia Comunitară Galaţi, Institutul pentru Solidaritate Socială, Constanţa pentru Ucraina
- Created editorial design for a foundation that teaches music to children from disadvantaged families (Stichting Leerorkest)

FRONT-END DEVELOPER @ CONTENTSPEED BUCHAREST

10/2017-07/2018

 Developed the front-end for the company website and for its e-commerce clients which included Sephora, E-pantofi and Autopneu.

FRONT-END DEVELOPER @ ENDOUBLE

10/2015-05/2017

AMSTERDAM

 Developed the front-end for recruiting websites in Benelux for companies such as Bol, Eneco, Sandd, Driscolls, Amc, Vumc or Booking.

FRONT-END DEVELOPER @ MOBGEN

01/2015-09/2015

AMSTERDAM

 Was responsible for the development and support of diverse websites such as Meld Misdaad Anoniem, Mobgen, flux.noii.se.

EDUCATION

GRAPHIC DESIGN FUNDAMENTALS @ CALARTS

2019

GRAPHIC DESIGN @ UNIVERSITY OF COLORADO BOULDER

2019

MASTER'S DEGREE IN COMPARATIVE ARTS AND MEDIA STUDIES @ VRIJE UNIVERSITEIT AMSTERDAM

2013-2014

BACHELOR'S DEGREE - ART HISTORY AND THEORY

2006-2009

@ ART UNIVERSITY BUCHAREST

OTHER SKILLS

- ENGLISH C2, FRENCH C1, ITALIAN B2, SPANISH B1, DUTCH A2
- CREATIVITY, EYE FOR DETAIL, COMMUNICATION SKILLS, POSITIVITY, ENERGY